

SUMMARY

I'm a seasoned front-end developer with a sense for aesthetics and interaction.

TECHNOLOGIES

Codina

County		
Python	HTML	
Java	CSS	
PHP	JavaScript	
Git	Bootstrap	
<u>C</u>		
Design —		
Adobe Photosh	op Balsami	q
Adobe Illustrator		
Work Flow -		
Scrum		

LANGUAGES

Chinese Mandarin (Native)

English (Proficient)

WENBO SHI

Front End Developer

\(: +1 905 966 0682

... http://individual.utoronto.ca/wenbo_shi

: 4065 Brickstone Mews #2107, Mississauga, ON L5B 0G3

PROFILE -

A meticulous web developer with one year of front-end development experience.

Passionate about responsive website design and keen on mobile-first development strategies. Independently produced WeChat mini-programs for corporate publicity.

Participated in the back-end development of the website of the Jiangsu Provincial Public Security Department.

EXPERIENCE -

PRODUCT MANAGER (INTERNSHIP)

Tencent / Naniing 2019 (Summer)

 Participate in the construction of the website backend of the Jiangsu Provincial Public Security Department, and use PHP to request the API interface to obtain data.

MEDIA CONVERGENCE (INTERNSHIP)

Jiangsu Science and Technology Association Nanjing 2019 (Summer)

• Responsibilities Participated in the Jiangsu-Taiwan Bionic Robot Competition.

MINISTER OF PROPAGANDA DEPARTMENT

CHINESE UNDERGRADUATE ASSOCIATION AT UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO University of Toronto 2018 - 2019

- Leading propaganda department and event department successfully organized the CUA (Chinese undergraduate association) freshmen meeting in the fall semester of 2018.
- Participate in the preparation of the 2019 Chinese New Year Spring Festival Gala.

MINISTER OF MEDIA

CHANNEL 6IX (THE PHOTOGRAPHY CLUB OF UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO) University of Toronto 2017 - 2018

- Restarted this department and expanded it from 3 members to 20 members.
- · Leading members successfully hosted video editing training.
- Leading members take multiple microfilms.

EDUCATION

MAJOR - COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Toronto 2017 - Present

MAJOR - COMMUNICATION, CULTURE, INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY

University of Toronto 2017 - Present